A Guide to the Frank Repass Brown Papers, 2004.3
Special Collections, Kegley Library, Wytheville Community College
- Series XII. Photographs. Undated., 8 envelopes. (Box 8)
  - Envelope 3. Repass Family. Undated., 8 photographs.
    Envelope contains 8 photographs of Seldon Repass, Mary E. Repass, Ellen M. Repass, Florence E. Repass, Anna M. Sharitz Repass, and tombstone of John Jacob Repass.
  - Envelope 4. Shannon Family. Undated., 9 photographs.
    Envelope contains 9 photographs of Dale Shannon, Brown Shannon, Marion Shannon, Jerome Shannon, Dallas Shannon, Thomas B. Shannon, George D. Shannon, George Shannon, and Carrie Brown Shannon.
  - Envelope 5. Umberger Family. Undated., 7 photographs.
    Envelope contains 7 photographs of Ella G. Repass Umberger, Chloe Umberger, Repass Umberger, Anna K. Umberger, Virginia A. Umberger, Lois E. Umberger, Stephen A. Umberger, and Margaret Repass Umberger.
  - Envelope 6. Other Families. Undated., 8 photographs, 8 greeting cards.
    Envelope includes 8 photographs of Joe Bill White, Jimmy White, Paul White, Mollie Neff, John Neff, Stephen Sharitz, Kate CasselL Schrock, Fletch Lloyd, Thomas Jonathan Jackson (Stonewall Jackson), Robert Edward Lee, and 8 greeting cards.
  - Envelope 7. Places. Undated., 10 photographs.
    Envelope contains 10 photographs of Brown farm, Quaker Church in Speedwell, Huddle School, and Frank Repass Brown house and garden.
  - Envelope 8. Unidentified. Undated., 20 photographs.
    Envelope contains 20 unidentified photographs.